These are...
But how did they get here?
It doesn't make sense.
Uh?
That's impossible.
Isn't it?
How did he get in here?
Mister Song.
This means, they had to shut the
broadcast down for something, right?
Hm.
But why?
What's happening over there?
It's no good. Too much
confusion at the scene.
There must be a way
to confirm their status.
Gather all the intel we can.
Yes, sir.
Director!
So many viewers are calling in at once
that it's crashing the phone system!
They're demanding
we resume the broadcast!
And we would if we could!
But in case you haven't noticed, we
lost contact, so there's nothing to show!
Besides, what do we do if all
the S-ranks are already dead?
Hey! What's going on?
We need an update, right now!
-Are you still alive out there?
-Damn it!
My camera quit working!
Of all the times?
Iron!
Go.
I'm not following any of this.
Who are these shadows?
And how did Hunter Sung...
even get to the island?
Oh, there you are, and just in time.
But how the hell did you...
I can explain it later.
Let's take care of your
wounds in the meantime.
Here, this should help.
Huh?
Right. The system
won't let me hand these off.
You summoned that?
Your magic sure is handy.
Hunter Ma.
I need you to open your mouth.
Aah!
That's unreal.
I'm healed.
Completely.
She's still in bad shape.
Why isn't it working?
Damn, just like before, these can't
work when your health is too low.
And her aura is getting weaker.
Her wounds are too severe
for potions to heal.
We have to leave now.
I can clear a path for us.
-All right.
-Hold on!
-Huh?
They certainly swarm like
the bugs they are.
How are we gonna
take down so many of them?
Chairman Go!
Any news on the strike team?
No. Not yet.
Something's jamming all comms from the
island, but hopefully it's only temporary.
We can't get through to Japanese
command either. Not sure why.
Touched base
with the civilian media,
though, and the last thing
they saw was the black ant.
It's imperative
we get that signal back.
And I want those medic and
retrieval teams ready to move out.
Yes, sir!
You know, Jinchul.
This has to be the most I've ever
resented this aging body of mine.
Even if I'd be of no help to them,
I wish I could join the fight.
Chairman Go.
Instead...
all I can do is pray.
Stupid technology!
First the feed cuts then the whole dang TV
decides this is the perfect time to break!
We're jinxed!
Well, beating it up
won't fix it, honey.
Whatever.
I'll watch it in my room.
Bet my phone will have updates!
Maybe.
That girl is so restless.
I want answers, so explain.
Goto-san's vital signs
went silent, sir.
Right before the signal was cut.
He was confronted by a
powerful enemy, and likely killed.
-And the others?
-We haven't verified.
Well, figure it out!
Any further losses
will cost us in the next phase.
On it.
Goto got himself killed?
Useless moron.
What in the hell
is happening on that island?
Elites like Igris and Iron
are holding their own.
But the foot soldiers
aren't doing so hot.
Part of me wants
to boost their numbers.
I just wish that
I didn't have an audience.
-New plan.
-Hm?
We're not making any progress.
Time to try a more
aggressive strategy.
See that mage?
You all hang back
and stay behind him.
My other shadows will
deal with the ant problem.
If any of 'em do get past my
soldiers, make them regret it.
Easy enough. We can
handle a plan like that.
For sure!
One last thing.
Please keep what you're about
to see to yourselves.
Uh. Is he?
It came back already?
I thought it went after Goto.
Does that mean he lost?
There was no king outside.
Is he in here?
The one you call king?
I can't sense the shadow
I sent with Goto.
Now, I know why.
-Uh!
-Wait!
Is it you?
Are you the king of humans?
Cute.
They got bugs that can talk now.
Human.
Quite the remarkable aura.
Huh?
Okay.
But, you're still just a bug.
This might be too much even for him!
I guess we're about to see.
Uh?!
Director! The feed is up again!
Wha... Isn't he the...
It doesn't matter!
Let's just air it!
Sir!
You realize we'll be
broadcasting without any delay!
If something happens live,
we've no way to stop it getting out!
We already cut the broadcast once.
Can't get any worse than that!
-Do it!
-Yes! Right!
Our future, the battle, everything.
Is riding on this man!
I can't believe it!
Me neither.
He's really there!
No...
way.
Jinwoo?
He said he was just stepping out!
What the heck?
He better break this habit!
He made it there!
Thank you, Hunter Sung!
It's him all right.
But how'd he reach them?
Point is he did it,
I don't care how!
Let's put our faith in him!
Why would a mage
type get that close to it?
He underestimated that ant's power.
And got clobbered for it!
Weak.
You are no king.
Um. Hey, guys.
Are you sure that
Hunter Sung is a mage?
I'm not sure about anything
when it comes to him.
And I definitely didn't expect this.
He's pretty durable.
The exoskeleton maybe?
Their punches are insane!
Even as an A-rank,
I can barely stay on my feet!
I might pass out just
from the force of their magic!
Am I being overpowered?
How?
I do not understand.
How could a human be so strong?
Poison?
A mixture of toxins,
from the marine life here.
Its potency, amplified
by my magic power.
You will lose all ability
to move before long.
This is the end for you.
Die, human!
Seven KIA in a ten-man team?
Is that a joke?
No. It's the facts.
We were able to contact the three
survivors, and they confirmed it.
We lost over half our hunters?
This mission is a catastrophe!
Oh, and, we've also detected a
strong reading near the island's caldera.
We think it's whatever
beat Goto-san, sir.
How is it alive after fighting him?
And it's headed into the nest? Why?
No idea.
It could have some objective.
Or maybe it needs
a safe place to heal.
We don't know if
the Korean team is alive,
but if they are hanging on by
a thread, Goto's killer will cut it.
They'll fall easily in their state,
and the ants will be worn out
from fighting, too.
If we can strike down the strong
one, the others will just be fodder.
Victory is not lost!
Hurry up and recover
the three surviving S-ranks!
Once they've joined the second strike
team at sea, send them back to the island!
Those are your orders.
A chopper will be there soon.
Roger that.
He wants to move ahead
with plan nine.
Let's go.
It's hopeless.
That thing is a monster.
If we don't run, then we're history.
Get a grip!
No time for panic attacks!
Everyone who faced that ant is dead!
All S-ranks!
And you wanna volunteer to be next?
You're pathetic.
We don't have any choice.
Deal with it.
Wait, I thought
he was just poisoned.
He seems okay, but is he really?
At this point nothing Hunter
Sung does will surprise me.
So, you had a secret weapon.
Ah, I was wondering why
you were holding back earlier.
Maybe it's 'cause my
perception stat's gotten so high.
But I can sense his emotions.
He's anxious.
That makes two of us.
Huh?
I can't waste any more time.
This ends now!
Poison is ineffective and
tests of strength are pointless.
In that case...
Speed that is equal to mine...
...and growing even faster.
How is this possible?
Upgrade.
Mutilation.
What happened?
How?
'Course you regenerate.
What was that?
What in the world was that?
How dare you, you human?
You filthy human!
Boys, get 'em.
But...
I was born to be the
absolute strongest being.
I devour all, growing more powerful
with each enemy I consume.
I am supposed to be king.
I am supposed to...
Run away.
I must run away!
In order to survive,
I need to run away!
Get as far as possible!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry and escape!
They're running scared.
Can't say I blame them.
Did we just win?
Hunter Sung!
Her aura's fading.
We don't have much time
We have to get her to a doctor!
There should be a recovery
helicopter right outside!
-If we go now!
-No.
She won't she'll last that long.
So we stay?
Thought your potions
were useless on her.
I haven't tried this one.
The Elixir of Life even cured
Mom's Eternal Sleep.
This is, this is our last hope!
Huh?
No, no.
Did it not work?
I can't leave
the island fast enough.
I can't use potions.
I can't use Shadow Exchange
because of the cooldown time!
So what?
What? What the hell can I do?